Guide to the Griswold-Brewster Oral History Project, Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Griswold-Brewster Oral History Project, Yale University
1990-1993
RU 217
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.5
The records consist of audiotapes and transcripts of the Yale Griswold-Brewster Oral History Project.
Yale University. Griswold-Brewster Oral History Project
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 49 (YRG 49), Papers and projects on Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were a gift of the Griswold-Brewster history project, 1990-1995.
Conditions Governing Access
Series II is restricted. Several of the audiotapes for interviewees in Series III are restricted, restrictions are noted at the item level.
Original audiotapes and duplicating masters may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or pay for the creation of a use copy, retained by the repository, if none exists.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in three series: I. Transcripts. II. Restricted Transcripts. III. Audiotapes.
Biographical / Historical
The Griswold-Brewster Oral History Project documents Yale during the tenures of A. Whitney Griswold and Kingman Brewster, Jr. as presidents of Yale. The project was funded by a group of Kingman Brewster's colleagues after his death. Geoffrey Kabaservice managed the project and conducted the interviews.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of audiotapes and transcripts of the Yale Griswold-Brewster Oral History Project.
College presidents; Educators; Audiotapes; Oral histories (document genres); Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1919-1988; Griswold, Alfred Whitney, 1906-1963; Yale University -- History -- 20th Century; Yale University -- Presidents; Yale University. President's Office
- Transcripts, 1990-1992; Series I
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Acheson, Alice, 1990 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acheson, David, 1990 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ashby, Baron Eric, 1991 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Atkins, Elisha, 1992 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Beinecke, William S., 1991 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Belin, Gaspard D'Andelot, 1992 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Berliner, Robert, 1992 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bissell, Richard, Jr., 1991 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Blum, John M.
    - 1991 Mar 18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1992 Feb 11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1992 Mar 4 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1992 Apr 28 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bockelman, Charles, 1992 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Boell, Edgar
    - 1991 Oct 29 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1991 Nov 5 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bromley, D. Allan, 1992 May 27 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Brooks, Harvey, 1991 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Brown, Ralph Sharp, 1992 April 30 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Brustein, Robert (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1991 Oct 24 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1991 Nov 12 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1991 March 25 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bundy, William P.
    - 1991 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1992 Apr 24 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Campbell, Wallace III, 1991 December 5 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cannon, Beekman, 1992 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Chapin, Melville, 1992 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Chauncey, Henry, Jr.
    - 1992 Mar 22 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1993 Jul 13 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 1993 Jul 22 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Clark, Elias, 1992 March 11 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Clark, Russell Inslee, Jr.
    - 1993 Apr 8 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 1993 May 13 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Coffin, William Sloane, Jr., 1991 December 9 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Cooper, Richard N.
    - 1991 Nov 13 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 1992 Apr 8 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Cox, Archibald, 1991 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Craig, Gregory, 1991 April 9 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Culler, A. Dwight
    - 1992 Apr 10 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 1992 Apr 29 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Cunningham, Jack W., 1992 July 6 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Cutler, Lloyd N., 1991 April 9 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Dahl, Robert
    - 1991 Nov 19 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - 1992 Mar 9 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Danes, Gibson, 1992 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1991 March 26 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Doering, William von Eggers, 1991 September 5 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Doob, Leonard
    - 1990 Nov 6 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - 1990 Nov 9 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Eisenman, Alvin, 1992 August 4 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Embersits, Jack, 1992 June 15 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Erikson, Kai, 1992 March 9 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Fanton, Jonathan, 1992 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Farley, William H., Jr., 1991 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Fesler, James, 1990 September 11 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Fisher, Roger, 1990 October 25 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Fitt, Alfred, 1991 April 10 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Forman, Charles, 1992 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Fruton, Joseph
    - 1991 Aug 1 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - 1991 Aug 20 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Glennan, T. Keith, 1991 January 2 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Gray, Hanna Holborn, 1991 December 17 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Griswold, Erwin, 1991 April 10 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Griswold, Mary
    - 1990 Apr 18 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - 1990 Apr 25 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - 1992 Apr 4 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Hall, John Whitney, 1991 June 3 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Halsey, Ralph, Jr., 1992 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Haskins, Caryl, 1990 October 5 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Hersey, John, 1991 August 13 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Holden, Reuben A., IV
    - 1990 Jun 1 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - 1991 Mar 2 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Horowitz, William, 1991 May 7 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Howe, Arthur, Jr.
    - 1991 Apr 1 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - 1992 Jul 18 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Howe, Harold, II, 1990 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Jackson, William E., 1991 September 10 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Kagan, Donald, 1992 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Katz, Milton, 1990 August 13 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Kernan, Alvin, 1991 May 11 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Kessen, William, 1992 June 2 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Lane, Robert, 1991 June 28 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Lawrence, Robert, 1992 April 6 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Levi, Edward, 1991 December 19 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Lieberman, Joseph, 1992 July 7 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Liebert, Herman W., 1991 December 5 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Lindblom, Charles Edward, 1991 June 3 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Lindsay, John, 1992 March 12 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Lipson, Leon, 1992 July 28 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - McDougal, Myers S., 1991 January 31 (Box 7, Folder 90a)
  - Mack, Maynard
    - 1990 Oct 16 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - 1991 Feb 20 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Marshall, Burke, 1992 April 27 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Martz, Louis, 1991 October 2 (Box 7, Folder 94 - 95)
  - May, Georges
    - 1991 Mar 19 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - 1992 Feb 20 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - 1992 Mar 16 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - 1992 Apr 22 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1990 May 21 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas C.
    - 1990 Aug 7 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - 1991 Aug 14 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Miller, J. Irwin, 1991 December 18 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Miller, John Perry
    - 1990 Sep 19 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - 1991 Apr 26 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Miller, Spencer Fyler, 1992 April 21 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Morgan, Edmund, 1991 March 21 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Norall, Frank
    - 1991 Jun 14 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - 1991 Jun 20 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Noss, Luther, 1992 July 2 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Perkins, James, 1991 August 3 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Pickett, Lawrence, 1991 December 10 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Pierson, George Wilson
    - 1990 May 24 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - 1991 Apr 4 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - 1991 Apr 22 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - 1992 Jul 14 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Pollak, Louis, 1992 May 18 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Pope, John, 1991 April 23 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon, 1991 January 4 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Rudin, Harry, 1990 November 2 (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Sandweiss, Jack, 1992 May 1 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Schmoke, Kurt Lidell, 1992 May 22 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Schrader, George, 1991 December 9 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Scranton, William Warren, 1992 July 16 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Scully, Vincent, 1991 May 6 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Simon, John Gerald, 1991 June 22 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Sloman, Albert, 1991 June 21 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Smith, Gaddis
    - 1991 Mar 19 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - 1992 Jul 28 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Smith, John Edwin, 1992 July 21 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Soifer, Aviam, 1991 September 6 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Stack, William J., 1992 August 3 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Stewart, Zeph, 1991 November 25 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Summers, Clyde, 1992 May 19 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Talbott, Strobe, 1991 April 10 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Taylor, Charles H.
    - 1992 Mar 2 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - 1992 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Thomson, James C. Jr.
    - 1990 Aug 13 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - 1990 Oct 27 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Tobin, James
    - 1991 Mar 20 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - 1992 Mar 19 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Trautman, Donald, 1990 October 24 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Trinkaus, John Philip, 1992 April 27 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Walker, Charles A., 1992 April 29 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Wasserman, Elga Ruth, 1992 May 7 (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Wegener, Peter Paul, 1992 July 20 (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Weiss, Paul, 1992 May 28 (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Westerfield, H. Bradford, 1991 October 28 (Box 12, Folder 148)
  - Whiteman, Harold B., Jr.
    - 1991 Mar 22 (Box 12, Folder 149)
    - 1991 May 2 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Wilkinson, John A., 1992 May 19 (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Williams, Frank O.H.
    - 1990 Sep 24 (Box 12, Folder 152)
    - 1991 Oct 11 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Woodward, C. Vann, 1991 November 6 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Zanger, Mark, 1992 April 7 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Zweig, Felix, 1991 November 6 (Box 12, Folder 156)
- Restricted Transcripts, 1990-1992; Series II
  Access is restricted. Written permission of interviewee required.
  - Bittker, Boris I., 1992 March 19 (Box 12A, Folder 1)
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1991 April 29 (Box 12A, Folder 2)
  - Ecklund, John
    - 1992 Jun 8 (Box 12A, Folder 3)
    - 1992 Jun 16 (Box 12A, Folder 4)
  - Lamar, Howard
    - 1992 Apr 28 (Box 12A, Folder 5)
    - 1992 May 6 (Box 12A, Folder 6)
  - McDougal, Myres S., 1991 January 31 (Box 12A, Folder 7)
    General
    The transcript is open for research. It has been transferred to the Transcripts series, box 7 folder 90a.
  - Morison, Elting, 1991 August 26 (Box 12A, Folder 8)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd, 1990 October 2 (Box 12A, Folder 9)
  - Rostow, Edna, 1991 January 3 (Box 12A, Folder 10)
  - Rostow, Eugen, 1990 November 21 (Box 12A, Folder 11)
  - Sewall, Richard B., 1991 February 13 (Box 12A, Folder 12)
- Audiotapes, 1990-1992; Series III
  Several of the audiotapes for interviewees in Series III are restricted, restrictions are noted at the item level.
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - Acheson, David, 1990 October 4; audiocassette (Box 238)
  - Ashby, Eric, 1991 June 19; audiocassette (Box 239)
  - Atkins, Elisha, 1992 April 7; audiocassette (Box 240)
  - Beinecke, William, 1991 August 14; audiocassette (Box 241)
  - Belin, G. D'Andelot, 1992 April 10; audiocassette (Box 242)
  - Berliner, Robert, 1992 March 30; audiocassette (Box 243)
  - Bissell, Richard, 1991 April 19; audiocassette (Box 244)
  - Bittker, Boris, 1992 March 19; audiocassette (Box 245)
  - Bittker, Boris, 1992 March 19; audiocassette (Box 246)
  - Blum, John
    - 1991 Mar 18, audiocassette (Box 247)
    - 1992 Feb 11, audiocassette (Box 248)
    - 1992 Feb 11, audiocassette (Box 249)
    - 1992 Mar 4, audiocassette (Box 13)
    - 1992 Mar 4, audiocassette (Box 14)
    - 1992 Apr 28, audiocassette (Box 15)
    - 1992 Apr 28, audiocassette (Box 16)
  - Bockelman, Charles, 1992 April 20; audiocassette (Box 17)
  - Boell, Edgar
    - 1991 Oct 29, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - 1991 Oct 29, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - 1991 Nov 5, audiocassette (Box 20)
  - Bromley, D. Allan, 1992 May 27; audiocassette (Box 21)
  - Brooks, Harvey, 1991 October 22; audiocassette (Box 22)
  - Brooks, Peter, 1992 August 5; audiocassette (Box 23)
  - Brown, Ralph, 1992 April 30; audiocassette (Box 24)
  - Brustein, Robert
    - 1991 Oct 24, audiocassette (Box 25)
    - 1991 Oct 24, audiocassette (Box 26)
    - 1991 Nov 12, audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Buckley, Jr., W.F., 1991 March 5; audiocassette (Box 28)
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1991 April 29; audiocassette (Box 29)
  - Bundy, William
    - 1991 May 10, audiocassette (Box 30)
    - 1992 Apr 24, audiocassette (Box 31)
    - 1992 Apr 24, audiocassette (Box 32)
  - Campbell, Wally, audiocassette (Box 33)
  - Cannon, Beekman, 1992 March 8; audiocassette (Box 34)
  - Cannon, Beekman, 1992 March 8; audiocassette (Box 35)
  - Chapin, Melville, 1992 April 13; audiocassette (Box 36)
  - Chauncy, Henry, Jr.
    - 1992 Mar 20, audiocassette (Box 37)
    - 1993 Jul 13, audiocassette (Box 38)
    - 1993 Jul 22, audiocassette (Box 39)
  - Clark, Eli
    - 1991 Mar 5, audiocassette (Box 40)
    - 1991 Mar 5, audiocassette (Box 41)
    - 1992 Mar 11, audiocassette (Box 42)
    - 1992 Mar 11, audiocassette (Box 43)
  - Clark, R. Inslee
    - 1993 Apr 5, audiocassette (Box 44)
    - 1993 Apr 8, audiocassette (Box 45)
    - 1993 May 13, audiocassette (Box 46)
    - 1993 May 13, audiocassette (Box 47)
  - Coffin, William Sloane, 1991 December 9; audiocassette (Box 48)
  - Coffin, William Sloane, 1991 December 9; audiocassette (Box 49)
  - Cooper, Richard
    - 1991 Nov 13, audiocassette (Box 50)
    - 1992 Apr 8, audiocassette (Box 51)
  - Cox, Archibald, 1991 November 13; audiocassette (Box 52)
  - Craig, Greg, 1991 April 9; audiocassette (Box 53)
  - Culler, A. Dwight, 1992 April 29; audiocassette (Box 54)
  - Cunningham, Jack, 1992 July 6; audiocassette (Box 55)
  - Cunningham, Jack, 1992 July 6; audiocassette (Box 56)
  - Cutler, Lloyd, 1991 April 9; audiocassette (Box 57)
  - Dahl, Robert
    - 1991 Nov 19, audiocassette (Box 58)
    - 1992 Mar 9, audiocassette (Box 59)
  - Danes, Gibson, 1992 May 4; audiocassette (Box 60)
  - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1991 March 26; audiocassette (Box 61)
    - Duplicating master (Box 61D)
  - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1991 March 26; audiocassette (Box 62)
    - Duplicating master (Box 62D)
  - Doering, William von E., 1991 September 5; audiocassette (Box 63)
  - Doob, Leonard
    - 1990 Nov 6, audiocassette (Box 64)
    - 1990 Nov 9, audiocassette (Box 65)
  - Ecklund, John
    - 1992 Jun 8, audiocassette (Box 66)
      Restricted
    - 1992 Jun 8, audiocassette (Box 67)
    - 1992 Jun 16, audiocassette (Box 68)
    - 1992 Jun 16, audiocassette (Box 69)
  - Eisenman, Alvin, 1992 August 4; audiocassette (Box 70)
  - Embersits, Jack, 1992 June 15; audiocassette (Box 71)
  - Erikson, Kai, 1992 March 9; audiocassette (Box 72)
  - Erikson, Kai, 1992 March 9; audiocassette (Box 73)
  - Fanton, Jon, 1992 July 18; audiocassette (Box 74)
  - Farley, Jr., William, 1991 December 16; audiocassette (Box 75)
  - Fesler, James, 1990 September 11; audiocassette (Box 76)
  - Fesler, James, 1990 September 11; audiocassette (Box 77)
  - Fisher, Roger, 1990 October 25; audiocassette (Box 78)
  - Fitt, Al, 1991 April 10; audiocassette (Box 79)
  - Fitt, Al, 1991 April 10; audiocassette (Box 80)
  - Fruton, Joseph
    - 1991 Aug 1, audiocassette (Box 81)
    - 1991 Aug 20, audiocassette (Box 82)
  - Furman, Charles, 1992 May 1; audiocassette (Box 83)
  - Galston, Arthur, 1992 April 22; audiocassette (Box 84)
    - Duplicating Masters, 2
    - Use copies, 2 (Box 84Ua–84Ub)
  - Glennan, T, Keith, 1991 January 2; audiocassette (Box 85)
  - Glennan, T, Keith, 1991 January 2; audiocassette (Box 86)
  - Gray, Hanna, 1991 December 17; audiocassette (Box 87)
  - Gray, Hanna, 1991 December 17; audiocassette (Box 88)
  - Griswold, Erwin, 1991 April 10; audiocassette (Box 89)
  - Griswold, Mary
    - 1990 Apr 18, audiocassette (Box 90)
    - 1990 Apr 25, audiocassette (Box 91)
    - 1992 Apr 4, audiocassette (Box 92)
  - Hall, John, 1991 June 3; audiocassette (Box 93)
  - Halsey, Jr., Ralph, 1992 April 21; audiocassette (Box 94)
  - Haskins, Caryl, 1990 October 5; audiocassette (Box 95)
  - Haskins, Caryl, 1990 October 5; audiocassette (Box 96)
  - Hersey, John, 1991 August 18; audiocassette (Box 97)
  - Holden, Ben
    - 1990 Jun 1, audiocassette (Box 98)
    - 1990 Jun 1, audiocassette (Box 99)
    - 1991 Mar 2, audiocassette (Box 100)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 100U)
  - Horowitz, William, 1991 May 7; audiocassette (Box 101)
  - Howe, Arthur, 1991 April 1; audiocassette (Box 102)
  - Howe, Jr., Arthur, 1992 July 18; audiocassette (Box 103)
  - Howe, Harold, 1990 October 23; audiocassette (Box 104)
  - Howe, Harold, 1990 October 23; audiocassette (Box 105)
  - Jackson, William, 1991 September 10; audiocassette (Box 106)
  - Kagan, Don, 1992 June 9; audiocassette (Box 107)
  - Katz, Milton, 1990 August 13; audiocassette (Box 108)
  - Katz, Milton, 1990 August 13; audiocassette (Box 109)
  - Keniston, Ken, 1991 November 12; audiocassette (Box 110)
  - Kernan, Alvin, 1991 May 11; audiocassette (Box 111)
  - Kerr, Chester, 1990 July 10; audiocassette (Box 112)
  - Kerr, Chester, 1990 July 10; audiocassette (Box 113)
  - Kessen, William, 1992 June 2; audiocassette (Box 114)
  - Lamar, Howard
    - 1992 Apr 28, 1 (Box 115)
    - 1992 May 6, 1 (Box 116)
  - Lane, Robert, 1991 June 28; audiocassette (Box 117)
  - Lawrence, Robert A., 1992 April 6; audiocassette (Box 118)
  - Lee, Richard
    - 1990 Sep 5, audiocassette (Box 119)
    - 1990 Sep 12, audiocassette (Box 120)
    - 1990 Nov 19, audiocassette (Box 121)
    - 1991 Nov 18, audiocassette (Box 122)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 122U)
  - Levi, Ed, 1991 December 19; audiocassette (Box 123)
  - Lieberman, Joseph, 1992 July 7; audiocassette (Box 124)
  - Liebert, Herman, 1991 December 5; audiocassette (Box 125)
  - Lindblom, Charles, 1992 June 3; audiocassette (Box 126)
  - Lindsay, John, 1992 March 12; audiocassette (Box 127)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 127U)
  - Lipson, Leon, 1992 July 28; audiocassette (Box 128)
  - Mack, Maynard
    - 1990 Oct 16, audiocassette (Box 129)
    - 1991 Feb 19, audiocassette (Box 130)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 130U)
    - 1992 Jul 13, audiocassette (Box 131)
  - Martin, William, 1990 October 6; audiocassette (Box 132)
  - Martz, Louis
    - 1991 Oct 2, audiocassette (Box 133)
    - 1991 Oct 2, audiocassette (Box 134)
    - 1991 Oct 29, audiocassette (Box 135)
    - 1991 Oct 29, audiocassette (Box 136)
  - Marshall, Burke, 1992 April 27; audiocassette (Box 137)
  - May, Georges
    - 1991 Mar 19, audiocassette (Box 138)
    - 1991 Mar 19, audiocassette (Box 139)
    - 1992 Feb 20, audiocassette (Box 140)
    - 1992 Feb 20, audiocassette (Box 141)
    - 1992 Mar 16, audiocassette (Box 142)
    - 1992 Apr 22, audiocassette (Box 143)
  - McDougal, Myres, 1991 January 31; audiocassette (Box 144)
  - McDougal, Myres, 1991 January 31; audiocassette (Box 145)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1990 May 21; audiocassette (Box 146)
  - Mendenhall, Tom
    - 1990 Aug 7, audiocassette (Box 147)
    - 1990 Aug 7, audiocassette (Box 148)
    - 1991 Aug 14, audiocassette (Box 149)
  - Miller, J. Irwin, 1991 December 18; audiocassette (Box 150)
  - Miller, J. Irwin, 1991 December 18; audiocassette (Box 151)
  - Miller, John Perry
    - 1990 Sep 19, audiocassette (Box 152)
    - 1990 Sep 19, audiocassette (Box 153)
    - 1991 Apr 26, audiocassette (Box 154)
    - 1991 Apr 26, audiocassette (Box 155)
  - Miller, Spencer, 1992 April 21; audiocassette (Box 156)
  - Morgan, Edmund, 1991 March 21; audiocassette (Box 157)
  - Morgan, Edmund, 1991 March 21; audiocassette (Box 158)
  - Morison, Elting, 1991 August 26; audiocassette (Box 159)
  - Morison, Elting, 1991 August 26; audiocassette (Box 160)
  - Noss, Luther, 1992 July 2; audiocassette (Box 161)
  - Norall, Frank
    - 1991 Jun 14, audiocassette (Box 162)
    - 1991 Jun 20, audiocassette (Box 163)
  - Perkins, James, 1992 May 20; audiocassette (Box 164)
  - Pickett, Larry, 1991 December 10; audiocassette (Box 165)
  - Pickett, Larry, 1991 December 10; audiocassette (Box 166)
  - Pierson, George
    - 1990 May 24, audiocassette (Box 167)
    - 1990 May 24, audiocassette (Box 168)
    - 1991 Apr 4, audiocassette (Box 169)
    - 1991 Apr 22, audiocassette (Box 170)
    - 1991 Apr 22, audiocassette (Box 171)
    - 1992 Jul 14, audiocassette (Box 172)
    - 1992 Jul 14, audiocassette (Box 173)
  - Pollak, Louis, 1992 May 18; audiocassette (Box 174)
  - Pope, John, 1991 April 23; audiocassette (Box 175)
  - Pope, John, 1991 April 23; audiocassette (Box 176)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd, 1990 October 2; audiocassette (Box 177)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd, 1990 October 2; audiocassette (Box 178)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon (one tape says Jan. 5; transcript says 4), 1991 January 4; audiocassette (Box 179)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 179U)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1990 November 21; audiocassette (Box 180)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1990 November 21; audiocassette (Box 181)
  - Rostow, Edna, 1991 January 3; audiocassette (Box 182)
  - Rostow, Edna, 1991 January 3; audiocassette (Box 183)
  - Rudin, Harry, 1990 November 2; audiocassette (Box 184)
  - Sandweiss, Jack, 1992 May 1; audiocassette (Box 185)
  - Schmoke, Kurt, 1992 May 22; audiocassette (Box 186)
  - Schrader, George, 1991 December 9; audiocassette (Box 187)
  - Schrader, George, 1991 December 9; audiocassette (Box 188)
  - Scranton, William, 1992 July 16; audiocassette (Box 189)
  - Scully, Vincent, 1991 May 6; audiocassette (Box 190)
  - Sewall, Richard, 1991 February 13; audiocassette (Box 191)
  - Sewall, Richard, 1991 February 13; audiocassette (Box 192)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 192U)
  - Simon, John, 1992 June 22; audiocassette (Box 193)
  - Simon, John, 1992 June 22; audiocassette (Box 194)
  - Smith, Gaddis
    - 1991 Mar 18, audiocassette (Box 195)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 195U)
    - 1992 Jul 28, audiocassette (Box 196)
  - Smith, John, 1992 July 21; audiocassette (Box 197)
  - Smith, John, 1992 July 21; audiocassette (Box 198)
  - Soifer, Aviam, 1991 September 6; audiocassette (Box 199)
  - Streater, Ed, 1991 June 20; audiocassette (Box 200)
  - Stack, J. William, 1992 August 3; audiocassette (Box 201)
  - Stack, J. William, 1992 August 3; audiocassette (Box 202)
  - Stewart, Zeph, 1991 November 25; audiocassette (Box 203)
  - Summers, Clyde, 1992 May 19; audiocassette (Box 204)
  - Talbott, Strobe, 1991 April 10; audiocassette (Box 205)
  - Taylor, Charles
    - 1992 Mar 2, audiocassette (Box 206)
    - 1992 Mar 2, audiocassette (Box 207)
    - 1992 May 12, audiocassette (Box 208)
    - 1992 May 12, audiocassette (Box 209)
  - Thomson, Jim
    - 1990 Aug 13, audiocassette (Box 210)
    - 1990 Oct 27, audiocassette (Box 211)
  - Tilson, Catherine J., 1991 March 12; audiocassette (Box 212)
  - Tobin, James
    - 1991 Mar 20, audiocassette (Box 213)
    - 1992 Mar 19, audiocassette (Box 214)
  - Trautman, Donald, 1990 October 24; audiocassette (Box 215)
  - Trinkaus, John, 1992 April 27; audiocassette (Box 216)
  - Trinkaus, John, 1992 April 27; audiocassette (Box 217)
  - Vance, Cyrus, 1993 August 19; audiocassette (Box 218)
  - Wald, Florence, 1992 June 8; audiocassette (Box 219)
  - Walker, Charles, 1992 April 29; audiocassette (Box 220)
  - Wasserman, Elga, 1992 May 7; audiocassette (Box 221)